the views and opinions expressed in this
media or comments on this channel are
those of the speakers or authors and do
not necessarily reflect or represent the
views and opinions held by sun life
financial
now that you have your sun life policy
it's time param register manito online
but before that let me congratulate you
for having one and you have now started
with securing your financial life
let's get started
when you got your sun life policy
contract
benefits
and premium contribution mode
but one important information
from your contract is your policy number
and you will need this information
paramagapa register online so you will
have to take note of this
all you have to do is open up your
browser whether from your mobile phone
or computer and the address bar input
the official website non-sun life which
is www.sunlife.com.ph
then click sign at pacao penang is a
window click register now
put your email address account policy or
plan number your name and date of birth
then click register pakatapus9 you just
have to check your email and follow the
rest of the instructions
you will have to put your email address
and password to login
and from here you will now see all of
your existing live policies and mutual
funds and the specific products that you
have
and what else can you do from here
account you may change your email
address change your contact number
change address update notification
settings say gustamong update casa
premium contribution mobile sms and
e-notice or sms enter your mailing
address you could also change your
password from here
with your life policies demand for the
moment view i'm gonna assign a
beneficiary or beneficiaries modito very
with the makita and transaction history
and make a file claim with your mutual
funds naman in here you have the option
to add fun switch fund and redeem fun
pedi with the makita and contact details
in sun life detail and you may also see
from here the questions for clients
frequently asked also you may download
sun life after your ios or android
devices
so there you have it guys for more
information regarding sun life products
and financial solutions we have you may
contact your sunlight financial advisor
or you may also reach us through our
facebook account just look for norm on
finances
[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
you